axact.com 2019-06-24

# Privacy Policy At Axact | Axact

We respect the privacy of our online visitors as our own and have made it a primary concern. The main reason for collecting and storing visitor information is to improve customer services and the quality of the website. We are aware of our responsibility to maintain and use visitor information especially client information with utmost security and privacy. No matter what the circumstances, we DO NOT rent or sell any visitor/client information that we collect online. However, we do share information with third parties meeting under certain circumstances. You can find details about third-party information exchange and interactions by reading the point titled "Third Party Sharing".

Purpose 

The purpose of this policy is to describe why we collect personal information about our visitors, how we use the collected information, and under what circumstances we share it with third parties. The policy includes information about the choice you have in how we collect and use your personal information. 

Collection of Personal Information 

We collect a range of information for different purposes. 

The breakdown of the kinds of information we collect by visitor type is given below. 

General Queries and Comments 

  1. Name
  2. Email
  3. Phone/Cell Number
  4. Address
  5. City
  6. Country

Vendors & Business Associates

  1. Company Information
  2. Emergency Contact Information

Job Seekers

  1. Identification Information
  2. Educational Background
  3. Employment History

Use of Collected Information

Collected visitor information is used in a number of ways. Information is used to process general inquiries and requests. Client information is also saved and maintained in our databases and used to process Axact’s dealings with associates. Our clients, vendors and associates and job seekers might also receive updates regarding our site and services. We might use all collected information for any further improvement to the website and to the facilities offered by Axact at any given time. 

The information we collect from job seekers is used solely for the purpose of evaluating their suitability for a particular job. The information may be shared with relevant department managers and other management cadre officers for the sole purpose of ensuring the best candidate is hired. Job seekers can be sure that their data is stored with the strictest **confidentiality** and **respect for privacy**. 

Third-Party Sharing

Third party information sharing is done strictly for the purposes of maintaining and managing customer information, fulfilling promotional requirements and for communicating with clients and associates. The sharing is carried out on a contract basis and the Third Party is not authorized to use this information for any other purpose. 

We do not share any other information collected with Third parties. 

Security of Personal Information

We have made certain that the information submitted by the users of our website is well-protected against any misuse. The information is safeguarded during transmission using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology which encrypts all information submitted by the clients, associates and others. In this way, all your information is absolutely safe and secure.

Registered Account Access

Registered associates can access their personal accounts by signing in through our website. Registered accounts are given access to specialized areas where dealings with Axact can easily be conducted online.

Unsubscribing, Changing, or Deleting Accounts

All the user has to do is to contact us with the relevant information and we will take care of the rest. Once you request that you want the cancellation of any subscriptions, we will immediately implement it. However it is important to note that this measure will prevent other e-mail communication regarding any other requests or queries that you might have made.

The Use of Cookies

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that are transferred to the hard drives of the visitors’ computers through their Web browser. We use cookies to enable our systems to recognize the browsers of the users of our site and to remember their movement during previous visits in order to serve them better. 

The Help portion of the toolbar provides more information about ur information is absolutely safe and secure. Registered Account Access Registered associates can access their personal accounts by signing in through our website. Registered accounts are given access to specialized areas where dealings with Axact can easily be conducted online. Unsubscribing, Changing, or Deleting Accounts All the user has to do is to contact us with the relevant information and we will take care of the rest. Once you request that you want the cancellation of any subscriptions, we will immediately implement it. However it is important to note that this measure will prevent other e-mail communication regarding any other requests or queries that you might have made. The Use of Cookies Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that are transferred to the hard drives of the visitors’ computers through their Web browser. We use cookies to enable our systems to recognize the browsers of the users of our site and to remember their movement during previous visits in order to serve them better. The Help portion of the toolbar provides more information about cookies and how one can stop their browser from accepting new cookies, how to disable cookies, and how one can have the browser notify the user when a new cookie is received. However, cookies allow you to take full advantage of the top features at our site, and our company’s personal recommendation is that you leave them to be accepted.
